[Music: ‘He’s a Black Flame Dragon’ theme song]
[Calm music]
Why are you crying?
Because I cry, I definitely
(Juyeon) Looks more like an angel
(Edited) Oh, really
[sniffling sound]
Oh, come to think of it, when I first saw it too
You just did that, right?
[Embarrassed laughter]
Angel... gel?
Ha, then and now
You're so good at saying things like this so shamelessly
She really looks like an angel, what should I do?
Then and now
[Embarrassed laughter]
I'll make porridge for you, so sleep a little more.
[laughter]
[Sound of grass bugs crying]
(Edited) Before going to bed
Take one more pill.
Don’t forget
I'm completely cured?
Is it all better?
Really
Still eat it, just in case.
Are you really going?
(Juyeon) Will you wait a little longer?
(Edit) I have to go, it’s late.
Take some rest today
We can continue to be together from now on.
I understand
Soojeong, please go home and rest well.
[Calm music]
Thank you
[Happy laughter]
See you tomorrow
Go in carefully.
Contact me when you arrive
[Slowing down sound effect]
[Nostalgic music]
(Juyeon) I can’t do it.
I can't let you go
Stay together, keep going
[humorous music]
What's wrong?
When did I fall asleep?
[Door lock operating sound]
[bird chirping]
[Sound of door opening]
Baek Soo-jeong
(Edited) Dad, are you awake?
Oh, that's it
How did this happen?
I'm going back to work now...
(Wonseop) Did you stay with the head of the department?
Are you guys meeting again?
(Edited) Yes
Sujeong, that house is not an ordinary house.
Looking at that article, there are a lot of people looking at it.
(Wonseop) I think there are a lot of people who make that noise.
Dad, when did I do that?
Did you see that I care?
Manager, I really like you a lot.
So, can’t we just give permission?
[deep sigh]
[laughter]
What is permission
If it’s my daughter’s choice, I have to trust it.
[Calm music]
(Wonseop) But Sujeong-ah
Still, if it's hard, say it's hard
Don't hold back
Dad doesn't know anything else
You just need to be happy
That's enough
(Edited) Yes
Oh, I must be tired.
Uh, get ready for work quickly.
Yeah, okay
(Wonseop) Ah, but from now on you won’t be staying out...
Don't get caught
Oh, I'll never get caught!
[Sound of door opening]
I should say that I don't stay out!
[Sujeong’s happy laughter]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
(Yongjin) Director Ban
yes
(Yongjin) You have been dismissed as of today.
[dark music]
[Hyoseon’s sigh]
I knew it would be like this
with that mouth
Didn't you say there was no relationship?
Yes, Mr. Chairman.
two people
It certainly doesn't seem like anything is going on.
I'm sorry to disappoint you.
Thank you so much so far
[Call connection tone]
(Guide voice) Customer
I can't answer the phone...
[Call end sound]
[frustrated sigh]
The Chairman is really great too.
(Nana) Oh, did you get fired, Chief?
So suddenly?
(Junsu) This is with the team leader
Isn't it because of the scandal?
(Nana) Oh, no way
(Junsu) No, otherwise
There's no way to explain it [Meaningful music]
The project is in progress
In one day like this?
No matter what, it's dismissal.
(Junsu) Ah, our project is
How do you do it?
(Nana) Team leader
[sigh]
The general manager...
(Junsu) Ah, team leader
[Call connection tone]
(Voice guidance) Can't connect
It connects to voicemail...
(Edited) Manager
This is the general manager.
What happened all of a sudden?
Are you really in a hurry?
Now between two people
I guess you have no intention of hiding it?
(In-kyung) It’s okay.
Anyway, the Chairman knows everything now.
- Yes?
- Team Leader Baek
When did you enter and leave the manager’s house?
(In-kyung) Everything
It looks like they put a lot of surveillance on it.
[Sighing] That...
Director Kwon
I submitted my resignation.
- Why?
- I knew it all from the beginning.
But I hid it
[heavy music]
[Elevator arrival sound]
[Sound of elevator opening]
Director
Please take care of me
(In-kyung) Still
I have someone like Team Leader Baek next to me.
I feel relieved
[sigh]
[Call connection tone]
Manager
Chairman, where are you now?
[Heavy Music - Continued]
Chairman
How dare you come here?
Meeting desired by the Chairman
I know it's not
(Juyeon) But I’m swayed by my personal feelings
Avoiding Yongseong
There will never be
- So...
- (Hyoseon) If I disappoint you
You said it was over, right?
grandmother
If it’s for Yongseong’s sake
You know I've done everything
(Juyeon) I will do better in the future
As my grandson
I'll try harder
I thought it would be a substitute
I never thought it would be a defective product
[Calm music]
That's disgusting
That you are my bloodline
(Juyeon) Then what am I?
what?
Since my parents passed away
I can’t be sad to my heart’s content
I couldn't even be happy
(Juyeon) Because I was always an undeserving grandson
No matter how painful it is
Still, I persevere and don’t miss a single day
I tried
If you live the way you want
Maybe someday you will find out
So far so far
I lived according to my grandmother’s standards.
Even loving that one person
Is this not possible?
(Hyo-seon) No way!
The guy who wants to be the successor
Love?
That's also a subordinate
The daughter of the hardware store owner?
Unqualified from the beginning
I wasn't accepting it
Just before
Anyway, to my grandmother
He wasn't the right person
yes
[sigh]
[Pass recognition sound]
(Young Juyeon) I...
[Calm music - continued]
I will take my father's place
I thought it would be a substitute
I never thought it would be a defective product
(Hyo-seon) That’s disgusting.
That you are my bloodline
[light sigh]
[Juyeon’s devastated sigh]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
(Edited) Are you okay?
Contact me as soon as you see it.
[cell phone vibrating sound]
(Juyeon) I’m okay
I'm sorry for making you worry.
See you later after work.
(Edit) Where is it?
I'm off work now
[Calm music]
(Juyeon) Are you here?
Are you hungry?
What should we eat?
Director
To the Chairman, we just
It's okay to say we broke up
I really don't care
There is no need to deny our relationship.
It's not that kind of problem
I'm sorry, for no reason
Where should we go?
I'm anywhere now
I can go on a date
That's right
Can you do that now?
(Juyeon) Holding hands like this
Sounds good?
(Edited) Then now the performance
I can go see it with peace of mind.
(Juyeon) After my face is known
I thought I would never see a performance again
From the next regular performance
Can I go see it?
[Calm music - continued]
Shall we go see it together?
I'm so happy if I go with Sujeong.
What I've been doing alone so far
Now it's all with me, whatever it is
Good
All I need is Sujeong
I think everything will be okay
Then you'll be fine from now on
Because I will always be by your side
[Shinwon’s sigh]
(Shinwon) You don’t look worried, Mr.
[cell phone vibrating sound]
(Juyeon) I’m with Sujeong.
[Knocking sound]
- (Shin Won) Kim Shin Won
- (Identity) Uh
(Shin Won-mo) Why are you like this these days?
Is it hard to see your face?
You're looking at your girlfriend's face, right?
Who asks because they don't know that?
(Shin Won-mo) The day I came home
That's because it seems like less.
son
[Shinwon’s awkward laugh]
They say I don’t draw people.
(Shin Won-mo) I draw pictures like that.
(Shinwon) I just wanted to draw it once.
I think it would be nice to give it as a gift later.
(Shin Won-mo) My son
Looks like you've finally met the owner?
(Identity) Um
I think so, me too
[surprised gasp]
[Soft music]
Are you even thinking about getting married?
Well, I didn’t think about it that far.
Um, what should I say?
I want to stay together forever
I don't want to fall
(Shinwon) If we stay together for the rest of our lives like you two
I'm sure I'll be happy
[bird chirping]
(In-kyung) With the general manager
I never thought I'd see you dressed like this
(Juyeon) Because I’m not the boss anymore
Why did you do that?
Director Kwon is out of sight of the Chairman.
I took action
I don't understand
I
Since when did I truly respect the Chairman?
Do you know that you are following it?
(In-kyung) To the head of the department:
It may be a cruel thing to say, but
It was after I lost my son.
Looking at the strong appearance of the chairman at the time,
Ah, if you are like this
I can trust and follow you
I wanted to
You hate espresso, right?
Sometimes you go see a performance
Inside a package with a strange name
I didn't check what was in it.
Knowing all that
Why didn't you report it?
Because I want to become the person the president wants
You hid it.
[Calm music]
(In-kyung) Hiding and suppressing emotions
It may not have been easy, but you persevered.
That's what the Chairman and I really like.
They look a lot alike
Chairman's wish
I thought it was the appearance of a successor
Then this time too
(In-kyung) No
In the end, I too am attracted to affection.
I was an ordinary human being
[In-kyung laughs]
(In-kyung) A successor is good, too.
The general manager whom I have watched since I was young.
It's good to be happy with the person you love
Because I wanted to
[laughter]
Director Kwon
That's right
[light laughter]
Yes, me
[laughter]
Thanks for working together
Thank you
[light laughter]
What should I do now?
(edited)
[Mobile phone operation sound]
(main role)
(Shinwon) I’m almost in front of the store.
(Hajin) Huh?
Am I still on my way to grocery shopping?
(Shinwon) It’s okay, just wait, okay?
Because I used up to half of it
Do you really have to watch a movie today?
Suddenly like last time
Don't miss the hotel
[laughter]
I changed the navigation destination because I liked it.
It was Shinwon, right?
Oh my, really
We are so in sync
Because it's a mask
(Shinwon) Okay, see you later.
[bird chirping]
[Soobin’s surprised exclamation]
What is it?
What's going on at my house at this hour?
[Interesting music]
(Soobin) [Sighing] Then, tell your grandmother.
Abandoned
I lost everything to do
Write, this is perfect
Are you unemployed?
Are you the same as me?
[Humorous sound effects]
[humorous music]
Unemployed person
No... Oh, no?
What do you have to do?
to do
There is no
So come to my house
I was trying to wait for my sister.
That's not exactly the case
Ah, but my sister
What's so good about it?
Because it’s pretty
Maybe
Did you spin?
It's not a sin to fall in love
IC
stop
[Sound of vomiting]
(Soobin) Ah, because I feel like I’m going to throw up.
stop talking, please
and
Because you love me for who I am
[sigh]
I cried and cried because we broke up
When is the time to make a fuss?
They're both so in love
(Soobin) I’m hooked
Mr. Sujeong
Did you cry?
yes
My dad and I are like that too.
It's my first time seeing you cry so hard
(Subin) It’s so creepy...
Not this
Well, now that I think about it, it was like that in the past too.
Because of the black flame dragon or something
[Calm music]
Black flame dragon?
Ah, what is it, my sister’s first love?
(Soobin) Completely dark history
If you knew that I know everything
Are you going to bite your tongue and die?
Even then
Did you cry a lot?
That's right
Well, I haven’t eaten for a few days.
Dad was very worried too.
(Soobin) But I can’t show it again
It was a legendary case of unfilial piety.
Enjoy
yes
[sigh]
(Juyeon) Father!
Give me the heavy stuff.
[Wonseop’s embarrassed groan]
[light music]
Oh, what's going on here?
Oh, I don't know
Suddenly, you said you wanted to help dad.
(Wonseop) Oh, you must be busy.
I'm not busy, I'm unemployed.
(Juyeon) I will do my best to help you
I don't have the skills, but I have the power.
It seems like I have no strength
[Humorous sound effects]
Did you see it?
[Wonseop’s laughter]
Oh, then whatever comes along, okay?
-Me too?
- (Wonseop) Oh, please take care of me [lively music]
(Soobin) I, I...
no, i am today
Since school was closed, I decided to take a break.
- (Wonseop) Hey, Soobin, give me some monkey
- (Soobin) Oh
(Wonseop) Oh
What should I do first?
No, I don't have any skills.
(Wonseop) Oh, can you do this?
Hey, all you have to do is change the doorknob.
Of course, I
If you give it to me, I will come forward myself.
Let's solve it
(Wonseop) Oh, if you can’t do it, just tell me.
Well, our Sujeong
Well, I can do it with my eyes closed
I'm a person who can't do what I can't do
[Humorous sound effects]
(Main lead) Yes
Are you going to do it with your bare hands?
Please go and take a look
[Subin’s laments and sighs]
(Juyeon) This...
How does this...
If you do that, I have to attach it with bond.
- (Soobin) This
- (Main Cast) Oh
(Soobin) You can just do it like this, right?
[humorous music]
This
child
With this
Let me try to solve this.
(Juyeon) Ah, then I will take this
I'll try it myself
[Drill operating sound]
Be careful and don't get hurt...
(Juyeon) Then coat
I would appreciate it if you could leave it to me.
- (Subin) I will listen to you.
- (Main lead) Yes
(Soobin) Are these clothes expensive?
(Juyeon) Ah, well...
I don't know much
This is originally
[Drill operating sound]
(Soobin) Ah
No, no, no
Hey, if you don’t know this
It would be great if you asked me to tell you
[Soobin’s awkward laughter]
(Juyeon) Thanks for letting me know, yes
you can do well
- I... again...
- (Soobin) Can you do well?
[Drill operating sound]
Now...
[Humorous music-continued]
Wow
It works
Father!
(Juyeon) I am this important
mission accomplished
[Drill operating sound]
[Soobin laughs]
Can I just do the same thing like this?
[Subin’s muttering]
Conversely, solving is the same
Ah, why is there no answer?
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[Interesting music]
(Subin) What should I do, boyfriend?
uh?
[heavy music]
(Yong Jin) There is a lot of concern about the vacant position of general manager.
About the successor
In addition to Director Ban Joo-yeon,
[Puts down the pen]
I'm afraid there won't be anyone who can replace Juyeon Ban?
Yongseong Products
Call me Park Ji-cheol
(Yongjin) Yes
Oh, and
Team leader Baek Soo-jeong
Do it quietly
(Yongjin) Yes
[Sound of iron door coming down]
[Wonseop’s groans of difficulty]
[Wonseop’s sigh]
(Wonseop) Oh, well, I had a hard time today.
Let’s have dinner together
yes
I will enjoy it
(Subin) Do you know what it is?
Are you saying you enjoy eating it?
(Wonseop) Write, today
What else should I eat?
So should I do it?
I!
Although there is strength
It also has a home-made taste.
It looks like it's not there?
[Humorous sound effects]
[Interesting music]
[Flashy cutting sound]
[Sparkling sound effect]
(Soobin) Oh
[Soobin’s light smile]
No, dad all day
I think they're anxious to get points.
This is a bit of a win, right?
score?
Oh, he's my girlfriend's dad, he's my dad
[Wonseop’s awkward laugh]
(Wonseop) Oh, well, there’s no need for that, uh.
As long as our Sujeong is good, I
It's okay
(Subin) Boy, is it good?
Although I was secretly distrustful of you
- (Wonseop) Me?
- (Soobin) Yes
(Wonseop) Me? Oh, isn't it?
[Wonseop and Subin’s light laughter]
It's natural to be worried.
(Juyeon) What is the environment and situation I am in?
It's not ordinary
Even if you believe in Sujeong,
Because it's going to be hard for me to believe
My situation is like this now
Dad, you don’t have to worry
I will do my best
No matter what happens, Sujeong
I won't make you cry and I won't leave you alone.
[lively music]
I'm such a bad dad
Other than trusting my daughter
I didn't have anything to do for you
Thanks to you, I feel safe
I will do my best so you don't have to worry.
[Resolute laughter]
[Weary sigh]
[Door lock operating sound]
(Main role) Mr. Sujeong
Welcome
What is it?
(Edited) What is that hood?
(Wonseop) Hey, Sujeong, welcome
Let's eat together, okay?
Hey, Ban Seo-bang is really good at cooking.
[Wonseop’s laughter]
Ban, what?
When I was young, early education
I learned some cooking
- (Wonseop) Ah...
- (Main lead) Yes
(Subin) Wow, this is really delicious, brother-in-law.
Braised ribs
Brother-in-law...
[laughter]
(Main role) Mr. Sujeong
I did it because Sujeong said she liked it.
Now...
[Juyeon sighs]
(Edited) No, what is all this?
(Juyeon) Now...
(edited) Wow
[Cheerful music - continued]
(Juyeon) Ah
[Embarrassed laughter]
(Edited) Hmm?
what?
Why is it so delicious?
[Happy laughter]
Right?
(Main lead) Accompaniment chronology
[Wonseop’s laughter]
(Wonseop) [Laughing] Ah, let’s eat too.
Ooh
[Subin’s satisfied moans]
(Soobin) Wow
[Wonseop’s satisfied laughter]
[Subin’s satisfied moans]
It's good
(Juyeon) At home like this
Talking while eating together
[Happy laughter]
After my parents passed away
Because it's my first time
(Subin) My brother-in-law, it must have been difficult.
(Wonseop) Go to sleep
(Juyeon) Yes?
Because you worked hard today
Oh, we'll have a drink together and sleep at my house.
[Calm music]
(Wonseop) Oh, well
Let’s eat breakfast together tomorrow, okay?
Uh, I'll make breakfast, uh.
Is that okay?
Oh, that's okay!
(Subin) Let’s sleep together in my room
Oh, your room is dirty, man, huh?
(Wonseop) How do you let a precious person sleep like that?
He sleeps with me in the master bedroom
(Subin) I...
Dad drags the tank by his nose.
I can't sleep well
Are you going to sleep in my room?
(Juyeon) It’s difficult because you want both.
my body is one
[laughter]
No, just sleep in my room.
(Wonseop, Subin) You’re crazy!
(Sujeong) No, what are you thinking?
Because I can sleep in the living room!
(Soobin) Oh, oh
[Wonseop’s snoring sound]
[Sound of door opening]
[Juyeon sighs]
[Sound of door closing]
[Soft music]
[Happy laughter]
[light sigh]
(edited)
[Knocking sound]
Why?
[upbeat music]
[surprised gasp]
[Happy laughter]
(Sujeong) I bought it to give to the head of the department.
When I think about it
I only bought one
If you put it in the refrigerator
I'm afraid my dad or Soobin will eat it.
I thought you were a dutiful daughter
I only think about myself too much
[Embarrassed laughter]
thank you
I'm still craving something sweet
Is it okay to drink alcohol?
I can't help it
What can kill me
Because it's just Sujeong.
(Edited) No, but
What on earth did you do today?
I rested while watching cartoons
Eating tteokbokki with my younger brother
I helped my father
(Juyeon) Oh, you know what?
I am a man who knows how to replace doorknobs.
[Sujeong’s surprised elasticity]
(Edited) Awesome, did you do that?
Wow, you're good at cooking and everything, right?
That's right
There's something you can do
You worked hard
Sujeong, did anything happen?
Yes, of course nothing happened.
That's good
While it's up, let's watch some comics.
(Juyeon) Is that so? Let's watch together
let me recommend
Good
(Juyeon) Um
This is it
I
Sometimes when I want to be combative
I'm just taking a look
[Surprisingly] Is this a handwritten autograph?
(Juyeon) Yes, that’s right
This is something I’m very proud of
It can be seen as one of the achievements.
[Sujeong laughs]
[Sound of Sujeong’s words]
[Juyeon’s voice]
(Sujeong) Why are you even sending me off?
I feel the same way
I want to take you to work.
Because breakfast meetings with family are more important
[Happy laughter]
Wasn’t it uncomfortable to sleep in?
Go home and sleep comfortably
Dad and Subin overdo it for no reason.
It was comfortable
more than home
Then I'm glad
Sujeong is the pretty daughter.
I'm glad you're my sister
Because thanks to you, I can also feel pretty
like family
[Calm music]
[Happy laughter]
Come on in, you'll be late for the breakfast meeting.
[light laughter]
I'll go
Mr. Crystal
I made a decision yesterday
It won't ring three times
So, have a nice trip.
Don't fall and don't get hurt
(Juyeon) Don’t worry about me any more
[light laughter]
[mail notification sound]
[Mouse operation sound]
[dark music]
[absurd gasping sound]
(Junsu) Huh? Team leader, what is this?
No, why even the team leader?
(Nana) No, this is absolutely ridiculous.
No, because of a scandal that isn't even true.
It can't be like this
Actually...
That's right
(Junsu) Yes?
(Nana) You said no, right then?
With the general manager?
I'm sorry, I really didn't mean it back then.
It's true that we're seeing each other now.
Uh, okay
[Sighing] Okay, that’s right.
(Edited) That’s right, unfair treatment.
Team leader
You're not going to just move on like this, are you?
(Junsu) Right?
(Edit) I’m busy
I'm so sorry it happened like this
Ah, team leader
[Support Team 1 sighs]
(Support Team 1) The woman who had a scandal with her grandson
Why did you send me here, huh?
You probably don't know how to do anything
(Support Team 2) So they sent it.
I can't do anything and then go out on my own
Hey there
I'll stay out of the way
(Edit) Annoying or bothersome thing
Please give me anything
I'm better than you think
There must be something you can do.
[Support Team 1 clears his throat]
[Support Team 2 sighs]
[Fire alarm operating sound]
(Support Team 1) What is it?
uh?
No, what's wrong with this?
It doesn't turn off at all
Huh? 1 hour?
Hey, hey!
I'll give it a try
(Support Team 2) Anyone
It's not something you can touch.
Electrician, firefighting equipment
I have a certificate, so it’s okay, right?
[Interesting music]
[Support Team 1’s surprised exclamation]
(Support Team 2) Done
What else should I do now?
[Employees muttering]
(Edited) Wait a minute
[Drill operating sound]
(Hyeju) No, everyone
I didn't go in, but in front of the door...
[sigh]
(Hyeju) Why are you doing this?
Weren’t you supposed to tolerate something like this?
Why are you so angry?
A junior that I hate to see
You don’t have to see me at the meeting.
I thought you would like it
What I hate about you is
It's because you can't stand it
(Hyeju) I try to please others
Throwing away all my pride
I came this far
You can't hold back anything
I said everything I had to say
All of a sudden, your pride is taken care of.
I thought you were the only one who was smart
I really hated that
[takes a breath]
But seeing you endure it like this
Do you hate this too?
Ugh, I hate it.
Baek Soo-jeong
- You better not do this...
- Senior
What I haven't tolerated so far is
It was to protect me.
(Edited) But
[Calm music]
To protect others
I guess I have to endure it too.
I'll go first
[Meaningful music]
(Nana, Seokhee) Hello?
[Drill operating sound]
(Junsu) Eat this while you’re at it.
- (Support Team 1) Ah, thank you.
- (Support Team 2) Thank you
thank you
He said he was the new general manager.
(Junsu) It’s really like this, Director Ban.
Is this the end?
[dark music]
(Anchor) Yongseong Department Store Strategic Planning Headquarters
Director Ban Ju-yeon is dismissed.
Director Park Ji-cheol, formerly of Yongseong Products,
I was newly selected
Especially this greeting
Yongseong Group Chairman Jeong Hyo-sun’s intentions
It is known to be strongly reflected
[cell phone vibrating sound]
Ah...
Are you okay?
I heard the news
(Edited) Sure.
[sigh]
Aren’t you overdoing it?
Does it look like that?
Yes, but if anyone is in this situation
Because I can't be okay
I need to manage my facial expressions better.
Oh, and I have a favor to ask you.
To the general manager
Could you please keep it a secret for a while?
[Calm music]
If you find out, you'll be upset.
I'd rather come to work
You can do it
I think too
I think that would be better
(Shinwon) If it’s Sujeong’s ability,
You can go anywhere
(Edited) I know, but
If I leave, there will be no room for me
It's all over
So as long as you can
I'll try my best
[Sound of grass bugs crying]
(Hajin) The company atmosphere is
It must be very confusing
How is Sujeong?
Your voice was strong when talking on the phone.
It's done
In reality, he was brave
It must be very difficult
Ah, he's like that, the harder it gets, the more
(Shinwon) Yes
[Sound of door opening]
[Door bell sounds]
(Hajin, Shinwon) Welcome!
- (Hajin) Mom?
- (Hajin) Oh, yes, Hajin.
Hey...
Who is this person?
[light music]
(Shinwon) Ah!
Hello, Mr. Hajin...
(Hajin) Uh, part-time job at a store.
(Ha Jin-mo) Hey!
Why do you have a part-time job when you can't even run a business?
So I just cut it.
(Hajin) Well, what have you worked on so far?
I'll send it to your account.
[Shinwon’s embarrassed groan]
(Hajin) I’m really, really sorry.
I'll contact you when I get home.
(ID) No, just
Can’t I just call him my boyfriend?
(Hajin) Then right away
I have to get married.
(Shinwon) Oh, I like it?
[Door bell sounds]
[Ex-husband’s awkward laughter]
(Ex-husband) Ha Jin-ah
It's been a while
Seobang Kim persuaded me to do something with him.
crazy bastard
(Ha Jin-mo) Hey! Hey, what's wrong with you?
To the person who came to get back together?
(Ex-husband) Ha, Ha Jin-ah
My mother wants this too.
Let's do well again
I also love the crab stew you make
I miss you so much
It's so lonely to be alone
Hey
[heavy music]
I spent my 20s with you
(Hajin) Until that time
Because I don’t want to regret it
They just divorced quietly.
So just stop talking bullshit
Go away
Seo Ha-jin
(Ha Jin-mo) Uyu
Why are you being so mean?
Even when Seobu Kim divorced
Because I thought of you
They even gave me money to open this store.
Do you think he gave that money with me in mind?
what?
then?
[Ex-husband’s awkward laughter]
(Ex-husband) Ha Jin-ah
(Hajin Mo) Oh my
What are you?
If you have a conscience
You shouldn't be doing this here.
(Shinwon) Especially in front of my mother
[absurd gasping sound]
(Hajin) I didn’t just get divorced.
This guy cheated
With another woman from work
What?
(Ha Jin-mo) Hey...
Well, that's it...
Now, now, mother-in-law, that...
It was just a mistake
- (Ex-husband) Mistake...
- (Ha Jin-mo) Mistake?
- (Ex-husband) Now, now, mother-in-law.
- (Hajin) Mistake?
(Ex-husband) I’m sorry, I mean...
[Hajin’s moans]
- (Identity) Oh, mother!
- (Hajin) Mom
- (Shinwon) Mother
- (Ha Jin-mo) Oh my, oh my
(Hajin) Mom
[ECG meter beeping sound]
Oh, I showed you everything.
[sigh]
[Hajin sighs]
[Ha Jin-mo sighs]
(Hajin Mo) Seo Hajin
Hey mom, are you awake?
[Hajin’s moans]
(Hajinbu) Honey, are you awake?
[Hajin Mo groans in frustration]
(Ha Jin-mo) This is it
Why didn't you tell your mom, huh?
[sigh]
I don't even know that
Like a fool, you only curse at my precious daughter.
[sigh]
It hurt, right?
It didn't hurt at all
It's a total mess now, huh?
[Ha Jin-mo’s soft moan]
(Ha Jin-mo) Oh my, oh my
It's my friend, just
My daughter is having trouble growing up...
[sigh]
[Shameless sigh]
I didn't tell you because I was afraid you'd be upset like this.
(Hajin) Oh my
Don’t you feel bad about blaming yourself?
- (Hajin) Ugh, Mom, Dad, Dad!
- (Ha Jin-bu) Honey, honey, calm down, anyway.
Now that you know, it's okay, okay?
[sigh]
Just put it in the refrigerator and take it
Even if I eat raw fish
He's a guy I can't get enough of, really.
[Hajinbu’s sigh]
(Ha Jin-bu) You, if that guy comes again
Uh, call dad first, okay?
(Hajin) Yes
(Ha Jin-bu) Did you understand?
Uh, okay.
(Ha Jin-mo) Hey
But that guy earlier
It's not that part-time job.
Boyfriend?
[lively music]
Did you have a boyfriend?
(Hajin) Oh
How old are you?
(Ha Jin-mo) Single? Or just single?
Hey, do you have any intention of getting married?
(Hajin) Ah, mom
(Ha Jin-mo) No
The person is just so tall, huh?
[Hajin and Hajin’s father sigh]
[Hajin laughs]
(Hajin) Oh, that’s enough, I like it now
You're fine, now go, go
[dark music]
(Yongjin) Baek Sujeong, I plan to leave quietly.
It doesn't look like anything at all
Because it stands out so much,
There seems to be more talk inside.
What should I do?
yes
Did you call me?
(Edited) Me?
Oh, I guess I was pressed while changing clothes.
Why are you changing your clothes?
Ah, that...
Oh, did I spill some water?
Did you eat that lunch?
Lunch is not yet
(Sujeong) Eat quickly
The more times like this
You know you have to eat well, right?
Uh, there wasn't much at home.
Why don't we go grocery shopping together after work? [Sound of door opening and closing]
[dark music]
Ah...
Mr. Crystal
What's wrong?
Because it happened
I'll get back to you
[Knocking sound]
[nervous music]
(Edited) Did you call me, Chairman?
earthly!
Why are you holding on?
Didn’t you understand what I meant by quietly leaving?
Director
Because you might come back.
[absurd sigh]
(Hyoseon) Ah
Was it because you were stupid?
Ban Ju-yeon
I hope to regain my position as successor
I know that greed, but
I am a person who is not qualified to do that
I have no intention of working for my company again.
So that place will be empty forever?
(Edited) If the head of the department is not qualified,
who is there
Can you sit down?
How can you be so confident?
To the general manager
Because the Chairman is my only family.
[heavy music]
(Edited) I want to be recognized by my only family
I tried because I wanted to be loved.
Someone who will try that hard
Do you think there will be another?
what?
Chairman too
Chairman, you don’t know what’s in your mind.
(Edit) All misfortunes
Because I blame my grandson
Are you comfortable?
And what I want back
It's not like a successor position.
This is the manager's family.
[Call connection tone]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
Hey, Juyeon, what's going on?
(Main lead) Brother
answer me honestly
[Employees muttering]
Oh, please take one of these.
(Support Team 1) What is this?
[Support Team 1’s surprised groan]
How do you feel?
Don’t you feel like your fatigue is going away?
All I have to do is move this today, right?
(Support Team 1) Yes
Hey, after all, I have a young friend.
Sounds good, huh?
[Support Team 2’s laughter]
There's a lot of fighting too
[Support Team 1 and Support Team 2 laughing loudly]
[Embarrassed laughter]
[Sound of approaching footsteps]
(Support Team 2) Huh?
[Calm music]
(Juyeon) What are you doing?
I should have told you
No, it should have just come out right away, what the heck...
Why are you doing this?
why because of me
Are you experiencing something like this?
I'm afraid it's like this
(Sujeong) He thinks it’s because of him
I'm afraid you'll be upset
- That's why I couldn't say it.
- That's right.
(Juyeon) If it’s not me, it’s Sujeong
There is no reason to be disadvantaged.
Why do you keep putting up with it?
(Edited) One word from the Chairman
The effort and time I have put in at this company
Are you leaving without being ignored?
I chose and decided for myself.
For me who loves the director
Because there is a next time if it stays like this
So please respect it
my choice
Then I will choose too.
For Mr. Sujeong
(Hajin) Thank you
Ah, you don’t have to take me like this.
Aren’t you tired?
Not at all
For this reason, I have been
I guess I worked out hard.
[laughter]
(Shinwon) Oh, and
It would be difficult to carry this alone.
I should have taken you today
No, what is this all about?
(Hajin) Is this mine?
(Shinwon) Oh, I’m sorry
It's not Hajin's.
(Shinwon) Um...
Hajin's mother's
And speaking of stores.
How about installing some CCTV?
That ex-husband
It doesn't seem that good.
You don't know when it will come again
Mr. Shinwon
Well, I couldn't help it at the time.
I, Mr. Shinwon, told me
Why do you care so much?
It's uncomfortable
(Hajin) Oh, and my ex-husband
Especially your family?
I will accept the gift as much as I want.
(identity) Yes
Drive carefully.
[Sound of car door closing]
(Shinwon) Mr. Hajin
just told me
Did you draw a line?
But
that line
Can’t I just use something that doesn’t exist?
I
[Calm music]
It's fun to be with Hajin.
I’m excited and comfortable
So boring and painful
I want to do sad things together too
That's how Hajin's life
It's because I want to go deeper.
(Hajin) I don’t like that.
Don't you understand me?
(ID: I know)
What does Hajin hate?
I know what you're afraid of
- So...
- I didn't understand.
Then we can't do it.
[sigh]
Where are you two going?
(Nana) There is an agreement ceremony today, right?
Working together with the renewal project
(Seokhee) Oh, that’s from Hanasi
They provide a lot of support, right?
Yes, preparation is done with the team leader.
I did everything with the general manager.
[Sound of Junsu clicking his tongue]
[Nana and Junsu’s sigh]
[Elegant music plays]
- (Mayor) Hello, how are you?
- (Hyoseon) Oh my gosh
Wow, nice to meet you
[The mayor and Hyoseon greet each other]
- Please sit down, yes.
- (Mayor) Yes
(Yong Jin) Chairman
I think you should go out for a while.
(Host) Yes, from now on
To attract global tourists
Hanashi and Yongseong Department Store
Let’s start the business agreement ceremony.
First, this is Mayor Mo Young-soo of Hana City.
[Applause from attendees]
[Continuous camera shutter sound]
yes, next
(Junsu) Oh, I’m really sorry.
[mumbling sound]
[Emphasized sound effect]
[Continuous camera shutter sound]
[Splendid music]
It's an accompaniment.
my name
[Exciting music]
Ah, yes
(Moderator) Yongseong Department Store Strategic Planning Director
This is Director Ban Ju-yeon.
[Continuous camera shutter sound]
[Music: ‘That Guy is the Black Flame Dragon’ OST]
(Juyeon) Trying to kick out team leader Baek Soo-jeong
Please cancel that plan.
(Nana) Wow, team leader
I missed you so much
(Hyoseon) Instead, there is a condition.
(Juyeon) Renewal Project
It must be successful
(Edit) Don’t try to take it all on yourself.
We decided to lean on each other.
Don't be lonely
(Nana) Renewal commemorative performance
They said they would cancel the performance.
(Junsu) No, the opening is right around the corner, but now
(Ingyeong) If you fail,
Because you lose everything
(Main role) It's me, Black Flame Dragon